A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Other, 1907-1985; 9
  - Elevators, 9.1
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 189)
      Service Elevator Enclosure, North Elevation of Elevator Enclosures, West Elevation of Elevator Enclosures, Plan of Basement Floor, Plan of First Floor, Plan of Platform Between First and Second Floors, Plan of Second Floor, Scale Detail of Section at "A-A", Scale Detail of Section at "B-B", Scale Detail of Section at "C-C", Scale Detail Showing Saddle and Sheet Iron Fascine on Basement Floor, Written on the Back in Pencil, Service Elev-Enclosure, J. Williams Detail, @32"x43 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
  - Safes, 9.2
    - 4/1908, 711 (Office Copy) Number 684 (Folder 198)
      Plan of Upper Compartment and Lower Compartment, 7 7/8"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Mosler Safe Co.
    - undated, 711 (Office Copy) Number 684A -Second Copy Doesn't Have Office # (Folder 198)
      Revised Elevation, # 1-9 1/2"x15", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written in Pen, Three Adjustable Wood Shelves in Upper Compartment Instead of as Shown, 9 3/4"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Mosler Safe Co.
      Received 6/23/1908
    - 1982 March 19, 711 NY33 (Office Copy) Number 684b (Folder 199)
      Elevation of Revised Pressure System, 7 1/8"x14 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Mosler Safe Co.
      Received 6/23/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - undated, 711 (Office Copy) Sheet Number 2, Number 673 (Folder 199)
      (No Title) Plan, Elevation {Safe}, 15 1/2"x12 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Mosler Safe Co.
      Received 6/19/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - undated, 712 (Office Copy), Sheet Number 1, Number 672 (Folder 199)
      (No Title) Plan, Elevation {Safe}, 20 1/4"x19 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Mosler Safe Co.
    - undated, 1905 (Folder 199)
      Fire and Burglar Proof Safe for Owner's Chamber, 27 1/2"x23 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hall's Safe Co.
  - Hardware and Ornamental, 9.3
    - undated, 606 (Office Copy) (Folder 200)
      Bronze Rosettes for Mirrors, 8 1/4"x9 1/2" (Edge not cut straight), Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      Received 8/13/1917 Jas Gamble Rogers
    - undated, 767 NY33 (Folder 200)
      No Title, No Labels on the Drawing to Identify It {appears to be decorative molding}, @15"x22", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - 1982 March 19, 919 (Office Copy) (Folder 200)
      Drawing of Medicine Closets, Written on the Back in Pencil, Meyer-Sniffen Drawing Medicine Closet, 29 1/2"x10 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Meyer Sniffen Co., Fine Plumbing Fixtures
    - 5/9/1908, 919 (Office Copy) {Different from the Other 919} (Folder 200)
      EmEss Medicine Closets, Written on the Back in Black Pencil, Hardware Blue Print, 35 7/8"x12 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Meyer Sniffen Co., Fine Plumbing Fixtures
    - 3/12/1908, 920 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 1 (Folder 200)
      EmEss Paper Box, To Set into Recess in Wall, 23 3/4"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Meyer Sniffen Co., Fine Plumbing Fixtures
    - 8/12/1908, 1982 March 19; 1130 and No Number Listed, Glued onto Drawing 1130 (Folder 201)
      Details of Umbrella Rack, Plan "A", Plan "B", Details of Shoe Rack, 30 1/2"x47 1/8", (Smaller Piece) 6 1/4"x25", Diazo Blue Print, Small Drawing Attached, Typical Closet Trim, 10 1/4"x13 1/8" Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
      Approved 8/14/1908 A.F.B.
    - undated, 1181 (Office Copy) ,Second Copy Has No Number Listed (Folder 202)
      Detail of Marble Switch Covers for Rotary Switch Locations, #1-18 1/4"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-18 7/8"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print. Architects, Lord Electric Company
      Received 9/25/1908 Charles T. Wills and Hale and Rogers
    - 10/2/1908, 1187 (Folder 202)
      Full Size, Section Thro Upper Rail of Balustrade for the Harkness House, 8"x6 3/4", Tracing Paper, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - 11/24/1908, 1196 (Office Copy), Order Number 19570 (Folder 202)
      Full Size Section Showing Wilson's Blinds, Written on the Back in Pencil, Reception Room, Windows and Doors, 26"x17", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jas. G. Wilson Manufacturing Co.
    - 11/23/1910, 1204 (Office Copy) (Folder 203)
      Full Scale Drawing of Proposed Bronze and Glass Letter Box for Side Light of Inner Doorway, Plan, Front Elevation, Section, Rear Elevation, Written on the Back in Pen, Bronze Entrance Door, 43 1/4"x@29 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - undated, X1189 (Folder 203)
      Fire Tools, 41"x21 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Samuel Yellin, Metal Worker
      Received 2/28/1921 James Gamble Rogers
    - 1/8/1908, Revised 1/21/1908; No Number Listed (Folder 204)
      Full Size Detail of Damper Box in Fire Place Flues, Written on the Back in Pencil, F.S.D. of Damper Box in Fireplace Flues, 33 1/4"x23 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, G.A. Suter and Co.
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 204)
      Full Scale Detail of Plate Glass Switch Plate, 10 1/2"x7", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Lord Electric Company
      Received 6/26/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 204)
      Full Scale Detail of Wood Trim Switch Plate, 10 5/8"x7 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Lord Electric Company
    - undated, No Number Listed (Same Drawing as the one attached to 1130) (Folder 201)
      Typical Closet Trim, 10 1/4"x13 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
  - Miscellaneous/Unknown, 9.4
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 205)
      Drawing is torn into 2 large pieces, Drawing of Decorative Glass Panel, Upper Portion, 54 3/4"x19", Diazo Blue Print (There is no writing on the drawing), Lower Portion (Small Piece Fits in the lower Portion), @40 1/4"x14" and @5 1/2"x5 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, (Probably Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, NY 33; 10-Tube Roll Coverings and Labels (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Label: NY 33 Carpenter Work, Shop Drawing, Tube 13, Roll 2, E.S. Harkness Res., @16'x16", The backside is an old architectural drawing, Cloth Diazo Blue Print, Architects, (Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, NY 376 (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Label: E.S. Harkness, Music Room Alt., NY 376 Shop Drawings, Tracings with Tube 103 Roll 3, 19 1/4"x7 7/8", The backside is an old architectural drawing, Cloth Diazo Blue Print, Architects, (Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Label: Tube 380 Roll 9, Edward S. Harkness Residence, Trunk Room, 5th Ave and 75th St, NYC, Drgs-101-301-501, Prel Sketches, 20"x9 1/4", Brown Paper, Architects, (Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Covering and Label, Ed. S. Harkness-Res., 1 E 75th St NYC-# Sketches of Wall Cases in Reception Room, Tube 410 123 (written in pencil), Roll 10 7 (written in pencil), A-4 (Blue pencil), 2 stickers used as closures on both ends, 18"x16 7/8", Brown Paper, Architects, (Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Label, Ed. S. Harkness, Shop Drawings, Plumbing Plans-Tube 14, Bathroom Layouts Tube 4, 7 5/8"x14 1/4", Cloth Diazo Blue Print, Architects, (Hale and Rogers)
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Label, E.S. Harkness Res., Shop Dwgs #700-799, Shop Dwgs Unnumbered, Tube 15 Roll 2, 8"x@20 1/8", The backside is an old architectural drawing, Cloth Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Cover, E.S. Harkness Res., Electrical Appliances, Tube 15 Roll 3, Written in Pencil-A-9, 14 1/2"x7 3/4", The backside is an old architectural drawing, Cloth Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Cover, 1-A Alterations, Coffee Bar, Sky Light Details, 23 3/4"x@14", Brown Paper (Used for Shipping Packages), Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 1985, No Number Listed (Folder 206)
      Tube Roll Cover, Façade Roof Renovations-1985, Stramandinoli Plans, 18"x4 1/2", Brown Paper (Butcher Paper), Architects, Vincent Stramandinoli and Associates